are people gonna vote and why aren't people voting are we too stuck to our phones i mean
those are the things that keep me up hi hi my name is zachara nice to meet you michelle i was
just wondering because you said us not voting is what's keeping you up at night i thought it would
be the 26 000 bombs that your war criminal of a husband dropped i feel like that might be something
that would help would make me not sleep at night um and not worrying about why people aren't voting
but but but i can give you a couple of tips as to why people like myself are not voting um because
you're a war criminal of a husband and biden who's also uh genocide biden you know aren't the best
people and haven't made us feel very safe to vote um we're in the middle of a genocide babe
we're in the middle of a genocide um i'm watching babies um women and men be obliterated to pieces
um the same thing that your husband did when he was president um but i can break it down for you
so he he dropped over a thousand bombs in afghanistan um he dropped over 12 000 bombs
in syria um he dropped 12 000 bombs in iraq over 400 bombs in libya um and bombs in yemen bombs
and bombs in america um and bombs in america um and bombs in america um and bombs in america um
and bombs in america um and bombs in america um and bombs in america um and bombs in america um and bombs in america um